原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译:  glida    芝小士和番小茄   zoeyyyyy
翻译:  Eunice    洗七里   梦里赛皇妃多少
校对:  梦幻空花赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十四集
最新海外影视剧下载
深吸口气  姑娘们  我的人生之旅从今天开始
Breathe it in, girls. My journey begins today.
终于能给这个世界带来我引以为傲的事物
Finally bringing something into this world I can be proud of.
莱特兄弟小时候梦见过会飞的机器
As children, the Wright brothers dreamed of flying machines.
莱特兄弟发明了第一架飞机
奥普拉小时候梦见过在椅子下面藏礼物
Oprah dreamed of hiding presents under chairs.
美国知名主持人  常大手笔送礼物给观众
而我小时候梦过建造宏伟建筑
And I dreamed of building something magnificent.
最近 杰和我买了一块空地
Well, recently, Jay and I bought a vacant lot
准备在上面建邓菲塔
on which we are building Dunphy tower.
我愿意付出一切  换取回到过去的机会
What I wouldn't give to reach back in time
告诉画出这幅画的15岁梦想家
to tell the 15-year-old dreamer who drew this,
"我们成功了  孩子"
"We did it, kid."
克莱尔  你看起来真糟糕
Claire, you look terrible.
"谢谢"啊
Thanks.
不  我意思是你很紧绷
No. I mean, you're all locked up.
是的  是的
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
看来我明天帮你预订的水疗
I guess the Spa Day that I booked for you tomorrow
正是时候
came at the perfect time.
对  水疗
Oh, right, that.
我生日这天要特别顾虑歌洛莉亚的心情
I have to be very delicate with Gloria around my birthday.
去年  不知道发什么疯
Last year, for some insane reason,
她居然送给我
She got me this gift certificate
可笑的莎莎舞课程礼券
for ridiculous salsa-dancing lessons.
好像我真的会去一样  拜托
Like I'm ever gonna use that. Come on.
后来她不知道为什么
Anyway, somehow, she's convinced herself
就觉得我不"感激"她的礼物
I didn't "appreciate" her gifts.
你也知道
You know.
有些人就是戏太多
Some people.
明天公司可能会有点忙乱
So, tomorrow at work might be a little bit hectic.
最近公司有很多事
Just a lot of stuff going on at the office.
不是我不想去  我真的很想去
And it's not that I don't want to do it, 'cause I do.
省省吧  克莱尔  咱俩今年别再演这戏了
No, Claire, let's not do this dance again.
我们都知道你不喜欢跳舞
We all know how you feel about dancing.
真是值得骄傲的日子  菲尔
Proud, proud day, Phil.
谢谢  搭档
Thanks, partner.
也许我们该赶快开始
Maybe we should get this show on the road.
摄影师趁海莉不注意时
The photographer's been taking shots of Haley
一直在拍她
when she's not looking.
好奇怪  我并没有请摄影师啊
That's weird. I didn't hire a photographer.
邓菲  对吗  我是杰瑞德·库克
Dunphy, right? Jared Cook.
铲子挺好看的
Nice shovel.
谢谢  我自己上的漆
Thanks. I painted it myself.
这位是我的搭档  杰·普里契特
This is my partner, Jay Pritchett.
我代表杰塔科技公司而来  你有听说过我们吗
I represent Jetatech. Are you familiar with us?
完全没有
Not in the least.
你得原谅杰
Oh, you'll have to forgive Jay.
他有点反高科技
He's a bit of luddite.
反正我们公司就在隔壁第二栋
Anyway, our building is two doors down,
我们正打算扩大园区
and we're looking to expand our campus.
我们想买下这块地
We want this lot,
准备付给你们比买入价
and we're prepared to offer you
高20%的价格  外加你们其他开销
20% over what you paid plus expenses.
这个报价挺不错的  杰瑞
That's a nice offer, Jare,
但你好像没搞清楚状况
but I don't think you understand what's happening here.
这跟暴利无关
It's not about the huge profits.
我们在建造的是我女婿的梦想
We're building my son-in-law's dream,
而这栋建筑将会大获成功
and it's gonna be a giant success
因为他是个有远见的男人
because this is man of vision.
我可了解梦想了
Oh, I know all about dreams.
我还希望某天能进军加密封包交换领域呢
Someday, I hope to get into encrypted packet switching.
祝你们好运  先生们
Good luck to you, gentlemen.
杰  我有远见的双眼已被感动的泪水模糊
Jay, this man's vision just got blurry with tears.
你能不能控制一下你自己
Would you get ahold of yourself.
我刚说的那些鬼话都是为了抬高价格
I just said that crap to drive the price up.
他会回来的
He'll be back.
我不想要他回来
I don't want him to come back.
不管你刚说的是不是真心话  这真是我的梦想
Whether you meant it or not, this is my dream.
我们做这件事是为了赚钱
We're in this to make money.
我们会赚到的
And we will.
根据商业规划委员会赋予我的权力
By the power vested in me by the commercial zoning board,
我宣布正式破土动工
I do hereby officially break ground
未来要在这建起邓菲塔
on the future home of Dunphy tower.
这土还真硬
Oh, that's...strong soil.
这是个好兆头
That's a good omen.
我用弹簧高跷那招试试
I'm gonna pogo it.
还有人带铲子来了吗
Anybody else bring a shovel?
你终于来了  里面就是个噩梦
Oh, thank god you're here. It's a nightmare.
员工因为预算缩减的事都炸锅了
The staff is in an uproar about these budget cuts.
跟他们说以后再也没有加班费已经很糟了
Telling them there's no more overtime was bad,
但当我告诉他们以后再也不提供贝果了
but when I had to tell them there were no more bagels,
有人用杯子扔我的头呢
someone threw a cup at my head.
我不知道还能做什么
I don't know what else to do.
我们圣诞期间的销售额
Sales-wise we didn't exactly have
并没有达到我预想中的成绩
the Christmas I was hoping for.
圣诞节大家不送衣柜都送啥啊
What do people give each other, anyway?
我就随便提议一下
Well, just spitballing here --
也许我们可以炒掉仓库的肯尼
Maybe we could fire Kenny from the warehouse.
没有要炒掉任何人
No one's getting fired.
可是他常丑化模仿我
But he does a really hurtful impression of me.
来吧  各位  都围过来
come on, guys. Everybody gather round.
我跟你们一样不喜欢预算缩减的决定
I don't like these budget cuts any more than you do,
但我希望你们知道  我跟你们一条心
But I want you to know I'm in this with you.
我已经削减了我的开销
I've cut my expenses.
主管出差搭飞机都只坐经济舱
All the execs are flying coach.
但我想要你们觉得自己也有发声权
But I do want you to feel like you have a voice in this.
所以  我办公室的门不仅随时为你们开着
So, not only is my office door always open to you,
我甚至直接叫人把它给拆了
I've actually had it removed.
没有门所代表的意义很有震慑力  老板
That's a very powerful metaphor, boss.
肯尼  谢谢你让气氛保持轻松
Kenny, thanks for keeping it light.
太棒了
So good.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
你来这里干什么
What are you doing in here?
你说你太忙了
You said that you were too busy
没时间离开办公室去庆祝生日
to get away from the office to celebrate.
所以我把庆祝仪式带来公司
So I brought the celebration to you.
犀利
Snap.
-那是鱼子酱吗  -没错
- Is that caviar? - Yes!
还有美酒相配
And something to wash it down.
香槟耶
Oh, yay, champagne.
快给我搞扇门来
Get me a door.
如果你给我搭的这东西在科学展览不能获奖
If I don't win the science fair with this thing you built me,
比赛肯定有黑幕
It's rigged.
说得好  姐们
Amen, sister.
拜托  你们怎么不等我就开始了
Oh, come on, you started without me?
不  我们不等你就完工了
No, we finished without you.
是的  我们想搭个能正常运作的
Yeah, we wanted it work.
那我猜你们是故意弄得这么"简朴"
I guess you also wanted it to be really simplistic,
因为那里可以改良
Because right there, you can make it better
只要加一个...
If you just added --
好吧
Okay.
就那里
So, right there,
那里可以改良  只要加一个...
You can make it better if you just added --
你不是说你们已经完工了吗
Okay, I thought you said you were done!
米奇尔  我爱你
Okay, Mitchell, I love you.
但是呢
But...?
没有"但是"
No "But."
可是我们都知道我才是更技术型的爹
Yet we both know I'm the more mechanically-inclined daddy.
我的手也很巧的
I'm handy.
不知道这话能不能安慰到你
If it makes you feel any better,
我也一点没搭手
I didn't do anything, either.
不  没有安慰到我
No, that doesn't make me feel better.
你本该从这个过程中学习的
You're supposed to be learning from this.
我新学了一句脏话
I learned a new swear word.
我手被木刺扎了嘛  不过也值了
Uh, um, I got a splinter. It was worth it.
看着
Watch.
这就完了吗
Is that it?
我太不懂  因为我不是技术型的爹
I'm confused 'cause I'm not mechanically inclined.
您真幽默
Hardy-har-har.
没完  我只要稍作调整
No, I just need to make a little adjustment.
小心
Watch out!
我的天啊
Oh, my God! Oh! Oh!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
这不是设计里的
That's not part of it.
我尽快赶来了
I got here as quick as I could.
求求你告诉我是个好消息
Please tell me this is good news.
求求你告诉我这是挖到石油了
Please tell me that's oil.
挖到了一段横穿过这块地的下水道
Found a sewer line running straight through the property.
还有总水管
Also, a water main,
不知道为什么  还有大量甲烷
And for some reason, giant pockets of methane.
快和我说说  皮特
Talk to me, Pete.
我觉得我刚已经说了啊
I feel like I just did.
处理费要多少
How much is it gonna cost?
钱的话  少说得六位数
Money-wise, you're looking at mid-six-figures.
你说的六位数包括小数点后两位吗
When you say six, does that include the two-cent figures?
不包括
No.
另外  时间上可能要耽误一年
Plus, time-wise, you're looking at maybe a year delay
来申请水电许可  环境许可
with permits and utilities, environmental --
别跟我说了  皮特
Stop talking to me, Pete.
我的天  杰怎么来了
Oh, my God, why is Jay here?
我也给他打电话了
I called him, too.
如果他看到这些会叫停整个工程的
He'll shut this whole project down if he sees this.
找点胶合板把洞盖住
Put some plywood over the hole.
托尼  想办法盖住甲烷的气味
Tony, do what you can to cover the methane smell.
其他人  都装忙
Everybody else, just look busy.
怎么会这样
How could this happen?
今天有只瓢虫落在我肩头  还以为是吉兆
I had a ladybug land on my shoulder today.
遇到什么问题了
What's the problem?
问题是我饿了
Problem is I'm hungry.
解决方法是  走几步到小印度餐厅吃饭
The solution -- we're walking distance to Little India.
-我们走吧  -那是什么味道
- Shall we? - What's that smell?
嘘  那是皮特的体臭
Shh, that's -- that's Pete.
他对这事特别敏感  千万别提
He's, uh, very sensitive about it. Don't bring it up.
既然你来了
While I got you,
我想在这装个自行车架你说怎么样
I was thinking about putting in a bike rack over here.
-那是怎么回事  -我什么都没看见
- What the hell is that? - I didn't see anything.
我很肯定如果真有什么麻烦  会有人...
I'm sure if something was wrong, someone would --
一到下班时间大家就特别兴奋
Oh, they love quittin' time.
就像卡通《摩登原始人》一样
Just like "The Flintstones."
我开始怀疑
I'm starting to develop a theory
这些情况就是皮特打电话给我的原因
that maybe all this is related to why Pete called me.
杰  我觉得你的疑心病有点重
Jay, I think that's just a little paranoid.
好吧
Well, there...
的确是有点问题
There was one thing.
抱歉  这杯绝对是香草味的没错
Sorry. This one's definitely vanilla.
我还以为你点的是"摩卡咖啡"
I thought you said "Mocha."
我"不小心"做了杯我最喜欢的咖啡
Oops, I accidentally made my favorite drink.
多谢提点
Thanks for the tip.
我已经在这做了五年了
I've been working here for five years.
不开窍的话可做不了这么久
Didn't get this far by being stupid.
我在想今晚要不要在我家办个小派对
I'm thinking about having a little party at my place tonight.
走起吗  艾狗
You down, a-dogg?
如果"走起"代表参加
If "down" means attending
"艾狗"代表艾丽克斯  那绝对的
and "A-dogg" means Alex, then yes.
我本打算回学校时就辞掉咖啡店的工作
I thought I'd quit the coffee shop when I went back to school,
但我还挺喜欢这份工作的
But I'm kind of loving it.
再说  这份工作教会了我一件重要的事
Plus, it taught me something important.
如果你装成人们期待中的样子
If you pretend to be who people want you to be,
朋友要多少有多少
you can have as many friends as you want.
天啊  我要是能重读一次高中该多好
God, I would love another crack at high school.
天啊  他又来了
Oh, God, here he comes.
谁
Who?
这个40多岁的小矮子每周五都来
This little guy in his 40s -- here every friday.
总是点无比复杂的咖啡
Always has a super-complicated drink order.
艾丽克斯
Oh, hey, Alex.
我要特大杯榛子味的脱脂冰玛奇朵
I'll have a 20-ounce iced skinny hazelnut macchiato,
要无糖糖浆  双倍浓缩咖啡
sugar-free syrup, double shot of espresso,
薄冰  不能没有冰  不要奶泡
Light ice -- not no ice -- no whip.
多谢你来见我
Thank you for meeting with me.
我尽快赶来了
I came as fast as I could.
我对我男朋友说谎了
I lied to my boyfriend.
每个人在恋情刚开始的时候都这样
Everybody does it at the beginning of a relationship.
"我喜欢爵士"  "男人哭的时候超性感"
"Oh, I love jazz." "It's sexy when a man cries."
"你女儿好可爱"
"Your daughter is so sweet."
我呢  我告诉雷纳我喜欢他最爱的电视剧
Me -- I told Rainer I love his favorite show,
《权力的游戏》
"Game of thrones",
所以现在他要带我去动漫展
So now he's taking me to comic-con.
我根本不喜欢《权力的游戏》
I don't love "Game of thrones".
我连看都没看过
I've never even seen "Game of thrones".
另外郑重声明  他女儿就是个魔鬼
And for the record, his daughter is kind of a monster.
4小时要讲完全部挺辛苦
This is a lot to cover in four hours.
先说说对于乔治·R·R·马丁的这部巨作
Let's start with everything you know
你都知道些什么
about George R.R. Martin's masterwork.
我知道那人死了[还没]  里面有很多露奶
Well, I know this guy dies, there's lots of boobs,
还有...  宇宙飞船吗
and I want to say... a spaceship?
你还是别说了  这样还能快点
This will go a lot faster if you don't talk.
他算是我亲戚  但有点复杂
So, he's kind of related to me, but it's a long story.
没事
Hey, it's okay.
我们都来自混乱的大家庭
We all come from messed-up families.
我叔叔是我爸
My uncle's my dad.
班表出来了
Shift schedule is up.
搞啥鬼
What the literal hell?!
今天两班倒  明天早上六点上班
Double shift today and 6:00 A.M. tomorrow?
-这不公平  -管理层才不管我们死活
- That's not fair. - Management don't care.
今晚的派对得取消了
Party tonight is off.
啥也不会取消  艾狗会搞定的
Nothing is off. A-dogg is on it.
"艾狗"吗
"A-dogg"?
你别管
Let me have this.
你在顶上放一点奶油
So, you put a little bit of the cream on top.
然后
And then...
好的
Got it.
超棒的生日惊喜  结束了好遗憾
Terrific birthday surprise. Sorry it's over.
才刚刚开始
It's just starting.
接下来还有好多惊喜
I have a lot of surprises coming.
我要进来啦
Knockedy-knock-knock.
我该怎么做
Okay, what do I do?
你做什么了
What did you do?
是按摩啦
It's a massage!
让他们进来  小伙子
Let them in, young man.
我叫本  我们都见了30次了
It's Ben. We've met 30 times.
歌洛莉亚
Oh, Gloria.
好朋友
Friend.
我很感激你请按摩师的主意
Listen, while I appreciate the idea of a massage --
你不喜欢
You hate it.
你总是讨厌我的礼物  我干嘛还要尝试
You always hate my gifts. I don't even know why I try.
不不  请让我说完
No, no, please, uh, let me finish.
我一直觉得
I've always appreciated the thought
在办公室按摩是个好主意
of a massage in my office,
现在真的要实现啦
and now it's actually happening.
谢谢
Ah! Thank you.
两位美女  哪位是克莱尔
Which one of you lovelies is Claire?
-她是  -太好啦
- She is! - Oh, great.
给我来个短点的
Just give me the quick version, okay?
-90分钟  没问题  亲  -好吧
- 90 minutes. You got it, hon. - Okay.
我部门的人问还会不会提供咖啡
My department is asking if there's still gonna be coffee
还是他们得自己带
or if they have to start bringing it.
这是谁
Who -- who's this?
他在面试仓库里的那个职位
Uh, he's interviewing for a job in the warehouse.
他是叉车操作员
He's a, um, forklift operator.
没错  2017年了
That's right. It's 2017.
现在有好多叉车操作员是基佬呢
There are plenty of gay forklift drivers.
我不是基佬
I'm not gay.
没事儿  老兄  我很开明的
It's cool, bro. I'm woke.
太逗了
That's funny!
你跟他简直一样一样的
You sound just like that guy over there.
工作时间到了  我们要看看这些
Okay, it's back-to-work time. We got to take a look at these.
再见
Yeah. See ya later.
回聊
We'll catch up.
这太扯了
Okay, this is crazy.
我不需要做核磁共振
I don't need an MRI.
是你跟医生说能品尝出颜色才让你做的
The doctor ordered when you told her you could taste colors
还是用法国口音
in a french accent.
好吧
Oh -- all right.
我都不会法国口音
Well, I don't even do a french accent.
我也没说你模仿得好
I didn't say it was a good one.
两位  通常我们不会拖拉头部受伤的事情
Guys, we usually try to move the head injuries along.
好的
Yes. Okay.
这
Well, it's...
这太小了
It's just so small.
这比看起来的大
It's bigger than it looks.
你看  我脑子根本没问题
See, there's nothing wrong with my brain,
因为他那句话  我想到了三个绝佳的吐槽
'cause I have three funny comebacks to that.
小卡  别闹了  就听鲍比的吧
Cam, come on, let's listen to, uh, Bobby.
人家懂这自己是在干嘛
He knows what he's talking about.
我认为我们不能相信
I don't think we can really trust
一个名叫鲍比的成年人所说的任何话
anything a grown man named Bobby says.
好啦  亲爱的  没事的
Come on, honey, you got this.
罗伯特  你好
Okay. Uh, Robert, hi.
我能问件事吗...  是这样的
Can I have -- question. So, listen.
我知道这是个大磁铁
I know this is a giant magnet,
我有好多补牙
and I have a lot of fillings.
它们会穿过我脑袋被吸出来吗
Are they just gonna fly out of my head?
-从没发生过  -好吧
- That never happens. - Okay.
我正在服用补铁营养品
Um, I'm also on an iron supplement.
-那会...  -有影响吗  不
- Is that - An issue? No.
快上去台子吧
Let's just get you on that table, huh?
快点
Come on.
不  不行
No, okay, not happening.
我有阴影
I'm having flashbacks.
我不知道我有没有告诉过你
I don't know if I ever told you this,
小时候  我掉进井里过
But when I was kid, I fell into a well.
和也掉井里的杰西卡宝宝同一天
It happened the same day as baby Gessica,
1986年18个月大的杰西卡宝宝掉入井里
搜救人员花了连续58小时最后成功将她救出
但她得到所有的媒体关注
but she got all the press.
现在我还好受伤
It still stings.
人人都爱小宝宝
Everybody loves a baby,
却没一个人为我这个高大的少年祈祷
but not one single prayer for a husky teen
我可是头朝下被困井里大半个小时啊
who's stuck head-first in a well for the better part of an hour.
小卡  别这样
Okay, Cam, come on.
你得冷静下来  好吗
You have got to calm down, all right?
这一眨眼就结束了
It'll be over before you know it.
-要一个小时  -我  我做不到
- In an hour. - I'm... I can't!
-我不做了  不做了  -等等  小卡
- I'm done, I'm out! - Okay, wait, wait, Cam, Cam.
鲍比  能不能让我进去
Okay, Bobby, is it okay if I get in there
让小卡看到进去是不会怎么样的
to show Cam that it's all right?
有这个时间吗
Do we have time for that?
行啊  预约我4点的人内出血了
Sure, my 4:00 hemorrhaged.
你能别...  好吧
Can you not -- okay.
好了  瞧瞧  小卡
All right, look at this, Cam.
小心点
Just be careful.
很舒服
It's comfortable.
我们就在这儿
We've got you.
我很好  没事的
Okay, I'm good. Okay.
老实说  小卡  这里很平静
Actually, Cam, this is very peaceful.
那里简直是酷刑室
It was a torture chamber.
我刚进去一分钟就哭了
I was in there one minute, and I cried.
我感觉很闲适  真的  真的
I feel so rested. I do, I do, I really do.
该你上了  没事的
Now you. It's all good.
去吧  没事的
There you go. All right.
我就在你旁边陪着你
And I will be right here beside you.
除了病人  旁人禁止逗留
Uh, no one's allowed in here except the patient.
我就在你隔壁房间陪着你
I will be in the next room right beside you.
好了  戴上耳机
Okay, so put your headphones on.
他们会让你听些东西来转移注意力
They're gonna play you something to get your mind off of it.
这是应急按钮
This is a panic button.
需要出来就按这个
Just push it if you need to get out.
好吧  我想我可以的
Oh, okay. Well, I think I can do this.
"艾拉·格拉斯为您带来《美国生活》
"This American Life," I'm Ira Glass.
今日节目"初汪之恋"
Today's program -- "Puppy love."
我们将听到一个男人
We'll hear the story of a man
通过走丢的雪纳瑞犬遇到灵魂伴侣的故事
who met his soul mate through a lost schnauzer,
还有俄勒冈州库斯湾的一只小猎犬
a beagle from Coos Bay, Oregon,
当了一周市长
who, for one week, was mayor.
开始第一幕
And we start with act 1,
搜救柯利牧羊犬寻找
a search-and-rescue collie looking for his owner,
遭活埋18天的主人
who was buried alive for 18 days.
在喝自己的尿液一周后
After drinking his own urine for a week,
贺拉斯·劳顿再也无法忽视残酷的事实
Horace Laughton could no longer ignore the terrible truth --
他氧气不足了"
he was running out of oxygen."
救命  救命
H-help. Help!
救命  让我出去
Help! Get me out of here!
我要杀了你
Hey! I will kill you!
小卡  别这样  这很严肃
Cam, come on, this is serious.
天啊  我无法呼吸了
Oh, my god. I can't breathe.
我需要氧气
I need air.
我要氧气
I need air!
抱歉  他太孩子气了
I'm sorry. He is being such a baby, huh?
里面有摄像头  我看到你哭了
There's a camera in there. I watched you cry.
最后  员工应该对排班有发言权
And finally, employees should have a say in the shift schedule.
这样我们才能相应安排自己的生活
It would allow us to plan our lives accordingly
也会让缺勤日更少
and would result in fewer missed days.
总之  无发言权无动力
In summation, no caffeination without representation.
一句话  我被炒了吗
So, am I fired?
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
仿佛大杯咖啡里满溢出特大杯级的建议
Those are 20-ounce ideas in a 16-ounce cup.
我忽略了眼皮子底下的冉冉新星
I have overlooked a rising star right under my nose.
但这是...
But that's the --
是的  助理经理的围裙
Yes, the assistant manager's apron.
我不是为这个来的
I didn't come in here for that.
正因为这样所以才给你
That's exactly why you're getting it.
但我不能...
But I -- I can't.
天啊  太复杂了
Oh, my God, this is so confusing.
演过《圣诞精灵》的侏儒
So, the little guy from "Elf"...
提利昂·兰尼斯特
Tyrion Lannister.
随便  我不关心演员的名字
Whatever. I don't know actors' names.
那是他出演的角色名
接下来也都是《权力的游戏》剧中角色名
他是詹姆的弟弟还是瑟曦的
Is he Jaime's brother or Cersei's brother?
都是  詹姆和瑟曦是兄妹
Both -- Jaime and Cersei are brother and sister.
但他们刚还在塔里搞了  好扭曲
But they were just doing it in the tower. That is so twisted.
赶紧继续
Go on.
大伙  刚发生了超疯狂的事
Guys, the craziest thing just happened.
我进去提了一系列要求
I went in there with a list of demands.
结果却阴险地成功升职
And weaseled your way to a promotion.
不  相信我  一切都和原来一样
No, trust me -- n-nothing is going to change.
不过既然我都看到了
But while I'm staring at it,
你们哪个能找时间把垃圾丢了吗
would one of you guys mind taking out this trash at some point?
向助理经理问好[纳粹礼]
Heil, assistant manager.
不不不  这对我们都好
No, no, no, no, no! This is good for all of us.
现在我们内部有人了  就是我
Now we have someone on the inside -- me.
艾狗
A-dogg.
是"艾"道夫·希特勒吧
More like Adolf.
你把纳粹暴行想得也太小了吧
I-I-I think you're really minimizing that atrocity.
待会我来说
Now, let me do the talking.
好  我正好不想说
Good. I don't feel like talking.
实在是怀着这梦想30年
It's just you nurture a dream for 30 years,
最后眼睁睁看它像皮特的眉毛般烧毁了
only to see it go up in flames like Pete's eyebrow.
我感觉像是...
I feel like a part of --
说好的不说话呢
This is you not talking?
他来了  上
There he is. Go.
是你啊
Oh, it's you.
先告诉你一声
Now, before you say anything,
-我们还是不感兴趣  -好
- we're still not interested. - Okay.
但假如我们感兴趣
But if we were interested,
也要比你出的价高很多
it would take a hell of a lot more than what you offered.
那些下水道怎么办
What about all the sewage?
习惯成自然
You get used to it.
先生们  我出价时
Gentlemen, when I made that offer,
还没发现这些问题
we didn't know about any of the problems.
我们公司对那块地已经失去兴趣了
I'm afraid we're no longer interested.
杰瑞德  我挺欣赏你
Jared, I like you.
我们愿意接受原价加5%
We're willing to go 5%.
我说了  交易取消
Like I said, the offer's off the table.
要捎你们一程吗
You guys need a ride?
我自己有车  谢谢
I have a car. Thank you.
希望不是那边那台
Hope it's not that one over there.
我的狗还在里面呢
My dog is in that car!
阿多堵着门救他的朋友布兰·史塔克
And as Hodor blocked the door to save his friend Bran Stark,
布兰用余光看着年轻的阿多说
Bran had a vision of a younger Hodor saying,
"挡着门  挡着门
"Hold the door, hold the door.
挡着门"
Hold door."
最后  挡着门[阿多]变成他余生中
And finally, "Hodor," the only word he would say
说的唯一一句话
for the rest of his life,
而他的生命也到此终结
A life that was now ending.
他早就知道了
He knew.
阿多一直都知道
Hodor knew his whole life
救小伙伴是他的使命
that his destiny was to save his little friend.
就像你拯救了本要在动漫节上出糗的我
Just like you have saved me from embarrassment at comic-con,
谢谢你  曼尼
so thank you, Manny.
不客气  我得走了
My pleasure. I should get going.
我也是  得去换我的卡丽熙装扮了
Oh, my God, me too. I have to change into my Khaleesi costume.
我再多待个几分钟还是可以的
I could probably stick around for a few more minutes.
派对可以挪到周一
Maybe I'll move the party to Monday.
周一我有空
Oh! I'm free Monday.
咱们待会聊
Let's talk later.
别  求你们了  我从没想过背叛你们
No, please. I never meant to betray you.
你们的友谊比这个傻逼职位重要得多
Your friendship means more to me than this stupid apron.
傻逼
Stupid?
斯科特
Oh, Scott.
世上有很多人会为了围这围裙
There's a whole world of people
而争得头破血流
that would kill to wear this apron,
但这条路不属于我
but this just isn't my path.
这新增的职责令我感到被孤立
This extra responsibility has me feeling alienated.
一人之下万人之上何其孤单
It's lonely one step down from the top.
信不信由你
You may not believe this,
但我一人独霸天下更感寂寞
but it's even lonelier way up here.
在我往上爬的路上  我忘了自己的梦想
Somewhere on my climb, I forgot my own dream --
成为南加州都会区最出色的速度金属鼓手
to be the best damn speed-metal drummer in the Inland empire.
现在还不晚  斯科特
There's still time, Scott.
说得对  我辞职
You're right. I quit.
什么
What?
现在你是经理了
You are the manager now.
你们俩  来我家开派对  快
Hey, you two, party at my house. Come on!
-棒  -好
- Yeah. - Okay.
跟你说一声  有个马桶堵到满出来了
Oh, FYI, one of the toilets is overflowing.
不是吧  躲到屋顶
Seriously, the roof?
我到处找你呢
I've been looking for you everywhere.
我只想有点空间  呼吸一下新鲜空气
I just needed some space and some fresh air.
闻起来有一种紫紫的感觉
It smells so purple.
好了  快回去体检  快走
Okay, you're going in that tube. Come on.
你的力气就这么点吗
Seriously, that's as hard as you can pull?
我才不弱
I am not the weak one here.
你连这么简单的体检也不做
You're the one who won't even get a simple medical test.
怎么  害怕了
What are you -- scared?
你是胆小鬼吗
Huh? You're chicken?
对  都吓尿了
Yeah, and I thought I made that clear in there
难道还不够清楚吗
when I peed a little.
行  那你就安心地死去吧
Fine, you just go ahead and die.
我自己把莉莉抚养长大
And I'll raise Lily by myself,
她这辈子再也不会去任何农场或马戏团了
And she will never step foot in another farm or circus.
那我做鬼也不会放过你
I will haunt you.
或者你就去检查一下吧
Or you could just get your head checked
我们就不会因你害怕而失去了你
so we don't lose you over some stupid fear.
你知道1987年10月14日
Do you know what I went through in that well
我掉到井里的时候经历了什么吗
on October 14, 1987,
全世界的目光都聚焦在
while the whole world was focused
杰西卡那个小贱人身上
on that media whore Gessica?
她当时还小  不过我记得
She was a baby, but yeah.
太可怕了
It was hell.
我可能早就一命呜呼了
And I would not have survived
还好消防员找到方法
if those firemen wouldn't have figured out a way
把我小姑姑艾德娜送到井下
to lower my little aunt Edna into that well
摸着我的脚告诉我不会有事的
and touch my feet and tell me it was gonna be okay
我陪着你
and that I wasn't alone.
小卡  我要是能在里面陪你
Cam, if there's a way that I could be in there with you,
我一定去  可我...
I would, but I --
等等
Wait a minute.
很好
Hey, you're doing great.
好的  我就在你身边
Okay, I'm right there with you.
我陪着你
You're not alone.
谢谢
Thank you.
你真是个好丈夫
You're a good husband.
多谢夸奖
Oh, that's very sweet.
对了  小卡
Oh, and, Cam.
要是扫描发现你没事  你就吃屎吧
If the scan shows that you're fine, you can suck it,
因为非技术型的这位爹
because this mechanically-challenged daddy
一个人做了这个挠脚机器
made this foot-rubbing machine all by himself.
我做的  我做的
I did. I did this.
舒服吧
It's good, right?
看你已经开始放松了
I see you unclenching.
我怕被别人看见
I'm just concerned that other people are gonna see me.
麻烦别乱动
Keep still, please.
我说了  她在开会
I told you, she's in a meeting right now.
放开我的领带
Let -- let go of my tie.
你完全没有放松下来啊
You're not getting any looser.
好想知道原因哦
Oh, I wonder why.
快回去工作
Come on, get back to work.
老闻到你女朋友办公室飘来松露巧克力的味道
It's a little hard to focus with the smell of truffles
注意力好难集中
just wafting out of your girlfriend's office.
我女朋友是你们老板
My girlfriend is your boss, okay?
她也不是我女朋友
And she's not my girlfriend.
我不否认我们对彼此来电
I won't deny we have chemistry,
有某种似是而非  若即若离的情愫
A certain will-they, won't-they kind of vibe.
好了  各位  你们好
Okay, guys, hi.
如果你们能给我20分钟
If you could just give me 20 minutes
处理一下个人事务
to deal with a personal situation,
我保证处理完会出来给大家一个交代
I promise I will come out and address all of your concerns.
-里面是在干嘛  -对啊
- What is going on in there? - Yeah.
有一点医疗方面的事情
Well, um, it's a medical situation.
其实还挺难以启齿的
Actually, and it's kind of embarrassing,
我很感激大家在如此困难时刻的体谅包涵
So I appreciate your support in this difficult time.
这事得赶紧弄完  你还需要多久
We got to wrap this up. How long do you need?
最少15分钟
At least 15 minutes.
我给你5分钟
You got five.
女士  这工作已经很不容易了
Ma'am, this job is hard enough.
有个小问题
Uh, hey, so, small problem.
可以登
It can wait!
没有等不了的问题
Every problem can wait.
一边凉快去吧  这位先生
So now go, mister.
你不是吧  我都去过你家了
Come on, I've been in your home.
说吧  本  是什么事
All right, Ben. What is it?
今天是玛格丽特的生日
Today's Margaret's birthday... Uh-huh.
但是当时已经来不及取消蛋糕
...but it was too late to cancel the cake.
大家都看到蛋糕送来了
Everyone saw it get delivered.
没事  那就让他们吃蛋糕吧
It's fine. Let them eat cake.
什么  她是不是在开玩笑
What? Is she kidding?
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant!
克莱尔  深呼吸
Claire, breathe.
不要  才不要
No, no!
歌洛莉亚  够了
Gloria, we're done.
别冲我嚷嚷  我只是想哄你开心
Don't scream at me. I just wanted to make you happy.
而我也是在哄你开心
And I'm just trying to make you happy
因为你对别人喜不喜欢
because you're so damn sensitive
你的生日礼物这件事超级玻璃心
about me not liking your birthday presents.
而我今天最最不需要的就是这个
Come on, this is the last thing I needed today.
天啊  快看她的手
Oh, my God. Look at her hands.
她就在这里面做指甲吗
She's just been in here getting a manicure.
你的良心不痛吗
How do you sleep?
拿下她
Get her!
冷静点  乔茜
Whoa, whoa, back it up, Josie.
没有人要拿下她
Nobody's gonna get her.
我知道这场面看起来有点糟糕
I realize that the optics are a bit troubling,
尤其是在今天
Especially today.
一个你在里面喝着香槟
A day when you've been sipping champagne
而我们在外面超过一小时吃不到零食的一天
while we've gone over an hour without snacks.
够了
Enough!
你们这帮人真该觉得自己丢脸
You should all be ashamed of yourselves.
我都认识你们多久了
How long have I known you people?
多明  肯尼  乔茜
Dom, Kenny, Josie,
-两个赫姆  -你不是吧
- The two Herms. - Seriously?
你们所有人5点准时下班  而她从来不下班
You all go home at 5:00. This woman never punches out.
她回了家也很少睡觉
She goes home and never sleeps
因为她不停在想怎么让公司更好
because she's thinking how to make this company better.
你们看不出来她人都要废了吗
Can't you tell what a mess she has become?
看她有多神经紧绷  还开始抽抽
How tense she is, her awkward tics,
压力大磨牙都要把牙磨没了
The way she grinds her teeth to dust.
我觉得她应该被宠爱照顾一下
I think that she deserves some pampering.
你们都快滚出去吧
So now get out of here!
走吧  走吧
Let's go. Come on.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
对不起啦
I am sorry.
我今年真的想把送你礼物搞好
I just wanted to make it right this year.
有的  你真的做到了
Oh, you did. You really did.
那就好  现在回去坐好
Okay, good. So go back and sit down
因为抱你就像抱个衣帽架似地
Because hugging you is like hugging a coat rack.
好了
Okay.
很好
Oh, that's good.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我做了力所不能及的大梦
I dreamt too big.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
是我自己相信了你
I'm the one who believed in you.
也是你抬价把我们抬到太平间
You're also the one who overplayed his hand.
我们已经知道我们都犯了错误
We've already established mistakes were made.
现在该想想接下来该怎么走
We need to be thinking about next steps.
或许我们该盖个小一点的项目
Maybe we need to build something smaller,
比如一个很酷的小餐厅之类的
Like a cool restaurant or something.
我也想过  但谁会来这里吃啊
I've thought about that. Who's gonna come down here?
这里都没地方停车
There's nowhere to park.
天啊  就是这个了  停车场
Oh, my God, that's it -- a parking lot.
这主意还不错
That's not bad.
盖这个都不要什么成本
We could build it for nothing
而且很快就能把贷款给还上
and pay off the majority of the loan by tomorrow.
咱们还是换个地儿聊吧
Let's talk about this somewhere else.
或许15岁的菲尔的计划并没有错
Maybe 15-year-old Phil had it right.
有时候你只需要把你的梦想
Sometimes you have to look at your dream
换个角度看
from a different angle.
或许梦想一直都是个停车场
I guess it was a parking lot all along.
求你告诉我是晚餐做好了
Please tell me that's dinner.
-我要饿死了  -不  是大爸的闹钟
- I'm starving. - No, that's daddy's alarm.
因为脑震荡  我们不能让他
We can't let him nap for more than two hours
小睡超过两小时
because of the concussion.
看他睡的样子  多么平静安宁
Oh, look at him. He looks so peaceful.
他今天太辛苦了
He's had such a rough day.
我上次试着叫醒他的时候  他超不开心
When I tried to wake him up last time, he got so upset.
我来吧
I'll do it.
谁教你的啊
Who raised you?
好吧  温柔点啊
Fine, just be gentle, okay?
谢谢惠顾
Thanks.
还有  别碰这个
Also, don't touch this.
这是我的美术作业
It's my art project.
-我能帮忙你一起弄吗  -不能
- Oh, can I help you with that? - No.
大爸说应该他来帮  因为他比你有美术细胞
Daddy said he should because he's more artistic than you.
拿来
Okay.
怎么了  怎么了  咋啦
What?! What?! Why?!
太好了你还活着
So good you're alive